Guide to the Henry S. Kaplan Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Miscellaneous Materials, Series 8
  - 3x5" index cards from a file cabinet reflecting drawer and tab separators.
    - Drawer name: Liver and Mammary Tumors, Mitosis, Metastasis, Others
      - Drawer 18, Tab 6 - Melanoma
      - Drawer 18, Tab 7 - Metastasis
      - Drawer 18, Tab 8 - Microbial Physiol. Gen., incl. Osmotic Shock, Lysis, etc.
      - Drawer 18, Tab 9 - Mitosis
      - Drawer 18, Tab 10 - Nervous System Experimental
    - Drawer name: Nucleic Acids
      - Drawer 19, Tab 1 - Nucleic Acids - Reviews, Books, General
      - Drawer 19, Tab 2 - Nucleic Acids - Bibliographic
      - Drawer 19, Tab 3 - Nucleic Acids - Biogenesis, Isotope Incorp., Turnover, ER
      - Drawer 19, Tab 4 - RNA: Isolation, Purification, Structure
      - Drawer 19, Tab 5 - Nucleic Acids - Structure, Isolation, Purification.
      - Drawer 19, Tab 6 - Nucleic Acids and Precursors, Structoral Formulae, Pathways
      - Drawer 19, Tab 7 - Nucleic Acids and Precursors, Nutrition of Microorganisms and Biosynthesis
      - Drawer 19, Tab 8 - Nucleic Acids, Analytic Methods
      - Drawer 19, Tab 9 - Nucleic Acids Binding and Complexing Agents
      - Drawer 19, Tab 10 - Nucleic Acids Denaturation, Hybridize
      - Drawer 19, Tab 11 - DNA - Isolation, Purification, Structure
      - Drawer 19, Tab 12 - Nucleo Proteins
      - Drawer 19, Tab 13 - DNA Content/Cell, Bacterial
      - Drawer 19, Tab 14 - DNA Content, Viral
      - Drawer 19, Tab 15 - RNA Content, Viral
      - Drawer 19, Tab 16 - Nucleic Acids, Biological Activities of RNA
      - Drawer 19, Tab 17 - Nucleic Acids, Biological Activities of DNA
      - Drawer 19, Tab 18 - Nucleic Acids, Normal and Physiologic Changes in Tissues
      - Drawer 19, Tab 19 - Nucleic Acids, Studies in Tumors
      - Drawer 20, Tab 1 - Analytic Methods
      - Drawer 20, Tab 2 - Sequencing and Mapping, Techniques for DNA and RNA
      - Drawer 20, Tab 3 - Coding
      - Drawer 20, Tab 4 - DNA Replication Mechanism
      - Drawer 20, Tab 5 - Transcription; RNA Synthesis
      - Drawer 20, Tab 6 - Translation; Expression, Gene Products
      - Drawer 20, Tab 7 - Nucleic Acids - Enzymes, Enzymatic Studies
      - Drawer 20, Tab 8 - DNA Polymerase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 9 - RNA Polymerase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 10 - Restriction Endonucleases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 11 - Apurinic Endonuclease
      - Drawer 20, Tab 12 - RNA Synthetase (RNA-primed polymerase)
      - Drawer 20, Tab 13 - Ribonucleotide Reductase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 14 - RNA-Primed RNA Synthesis
      - Drawer 20, Tab 15 - Polynucleotide Phosphorylase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 16 - N.A. - Methylation
      - Drawer 20, Tab 17 - Nucleosidases + Nucleotidases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 18 - Polynucleotide Kinase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 19 - Ligases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 20 - Terminal Transferase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 21 - Endo-DNAases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 22 - Deaminases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 23 - N.A. Exonucleases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 24 - Transdeoxyribosylase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 25 - DNA Gyrase
      - Drawer 20, Tab 26 - Kinases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 27 - DNAases (Pancreatic Type)
      - Drawer 20, Tab 28 - Rec A Gene and Protein; DNA Recombination
      - Drawer 20, Tab 29 - REC B, C - Nuclease
      - Drawer 20, Tab 30 - DNA Unwinding Proteins
      - Drawer 20, Tab 31 - RNAases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 32 - Phosphatases, Phosphodiesterases
      - Drawer 20, Tab 33 - Enzymes of Purine, Biosynthesis and Conversion
      - Drawer 20, Tab 34 - Enzymes of Pyrim. Synth. and Interconversion
      - Drawer 20, Tab 35 - Thymine - Less Death and Induction
    - Drawer name: Ovary, Pituitary, Skin, Stomach, Testis, Thyroid Transplantation
      - Drawer 21, Tab 1 - Nutrition and Exper. CA
      - Drawer 21, Tab 2 - Ovary - Exp. Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 3 - Pancreas - Exp. Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 4 - Parabiosis
      - Drawer 21, Tab 5 - Photosensitizers
      - Drawer 21, Tab 6 - Pituitary - Exp. Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 7 - Skin - Experimental Carcinogenesis
      - Drawer 21, Tab 8 - Statistics
      - Drawer 21, Tab 9 - Spores
      - Drawer 21, Tab 10 - Spontaneous Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 11 - Stomach - Exper. CA
      - Drawer 21, Tab 12 - Testis - Exp. Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 13 - Thyroid - Exp. Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 14 - Transferring
      - Drawer 21, Tab 15 - Transplantation of Experimental Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 16 - Heterotransplantation of Human Tumors
      - Drawer 21, Tab 17 - Urethane
    - Drawer name: Virology
      - Drawer 22, Tab 1 - Viruses, Gen.
      - Drawer 22, Tab 2 - Viruses, Bact., Gen.
      - Drawer 22, Tab 3 - Virus, Bacterial - Induction, Lysogeny
      - Drawer 22, Tab 4 - Virus, Bact. - DNA
      - Drawer 22, Tab 5 - Virus, Bact. - RNA
      - Drawer 22, Tab 6 - Virus, Infectious N. A.
      - Drawer 22, Tab 7 - Virus, Bact 0X174 and other 1- Stranded DNA
      - Drawer 22, Tab 8 - Virus, RNA, 2-stranded
      - Drawer 22, Tab 9 - Viruses, Plant
      - Drawer 22, Tab 10 - Viruses, Animal
      - Drawer 22, Tab 11 - Colicins
      - Drawer 22, Tab 12 - Viruses-Chemical Inhibitors, Exper. Chemotherapy
      - Drawer 22, Tab 13 - Interferon
- Restricted Materials, Series 9
  - Restricted materials from throughout collection (Box 1)